この初心者課題では、
基本的な初心者チュートリアルから、
基本概念を多く使用し、非常に単純ではありますが
プレイすることができるゲームを作ります。
私達は、特定のGameObjectを収集する
玉転がしゲームを作っていきます。
新しいGameObjectを作成するためには、
これらのGameObjectへコンポーネントを加え、
そのプロパティに値を設定し、
ゲームを実行するとGameObjectが配置されます。
In our game the player will control a ball
rolling around the game board.
We will move the ball using physics and forces.
We will look at the input from the player
through the keyboard and we'll use those
inputs to apply forces to the ball, making it
move in our scene.
We will see how to detect contact between
the player's ball and the pick-up game objects.
and use these events to collect these
pick-up game objects.
When we are done we will have made a simple
roll-a-ball game where the player controls
the ball with the keyboard, picks up and
counts special collectable objects,
displays the current count and ends the game
when all of the game objects have
been picked up.
We won't need to import any assets for this project.
We won't be using models, textures,
sounds or animations for this assignment.
We will simply use the primitive shapes
like cubes, spheres and planes
provided by Unity.
To begin start with assignment 1 where we
setup our game and starting game objects.